You jerk-face!
(Bernadette:)What did you tell Howard?
You say there's something going on
between us? He thinks there is.
(Bernadette:)He's completely freaking out!
(Raj:)Please, come in.
(Leonard:)What the hell is wrong with you?
(Raj:)You were always so nice to me,
I thought maybe you liked me.
I'm nice to everyone!
(Penny:)- I'm sorry.
- Damn right, you're sorry.
(Bernadette:)And you tell Howard
there's never been anything between us.
(Raj:)I will. Hey, Bernadette.
(Howard:)- What?
- Do you think I have a shot with Penny?
(Bernadette:)Of course, you do. You're a cutie pie.
Any girl would be lucky to have you.
(Penny:)You know, I've done this before.
(Penny:)In kindergarten, I was supposed
to marry Jason Sorensen...
(Penny:)...but by the time my class got out there,
he was engaged to Chelsea HimmeIfarb.